Guide to the Vassar College Programs Scrapbooks, 1865-1982
Archives and Special Collections Library, Vassar College Libraries
Vassar College Programs Scrapbooks
1865-1982
Vassar College
15 cubic feet (70 volumes)
Archives and Special Collections Library, Vassar College Libraries
Scrapbooks containing programs relating to Vassar College events.
Administrative History
Vassar College was founded in 1861 and opened its doors in 1865.
Scope and Content Note
This collection consists of scrapbooks containing invitations, leaflets, pamphlets, programs, flyers, and other printed ephemera related to Vassar College programs and events. The first set of scrapbooks were created by the Office of the President; the compiler of the second set is unknown.
Access
This collection is open for research according to the
regulations of the Vassar College Archives and Special Collections Library
without any additional restrictions.
Related Materials
Additional programs and events ephemera are located in the Vassar College Programs and Events Collection.
Subject Headings
Organizations:
Vassar College
Subjects:
Women's colleges--New York (State)--Poughkeepsie
Document Types:
Printed ephemera; Programs; Scrapbooks
VCL Categories
Vassar College Events and Issues
Encoding Information
Encoded by Mark Seidl, July 2022. Updated by Emma Gronbeck, February 2023.
Container List
- Set 1. President's Office, 1865-1916
  - 1865-1893 (Volume 1)
  - 1880-1904 (Volume 2)
  - 1904-1916 (Volume 3)
- Set 2, 1866-1982
  - 1866 March - 1869 April (Volume 4)
  - 1869 May - 1871 June (Volume 5)
  - 1871 September - 1873 December (Volume 6)
  - 1874 January - 1876 February (Volume 7)
  - 1876 March - 1878 May (Volume 8)
  - 1878 June - 1880 November (Volume 9)
  - 1880 November - 1883 May (Volume 10)
  - 1883 June - 1886 December (Volume 11)
  - 1887 January - 1890 December (Volume 12)
  - 1891 January - 1894 November (Volume 13)
  - 1894 December - 1898 June (Volume 14)
  - 1898 September - 1903 June (Volume 15)
  - 1903 September 1908 June (Volume 16)
  - 1908 September - 1913 June (Volume 17)
  - 1913 October - 1916 June (Volume 18)
  - 1916 September - 1922 June (Volume 19)
  - 1922 September - 1924 June (Volume 20)
  - 1924 September - 1926 June (Volume 21)
  - 1926 October - 1928 June (Volume 22)
  - 1928 July - 1929 June (Volume 23)
  - 1929 September - 1930 June (Volume 24)
  - 1930 September - 1932 June (Volume 25)
  - 1932 September - 1933 June (Volume 26)
  - 1933 September - 1934 June (Volume 27)
  - 1934 September - 1935 June (Volume 28)
  - 1935 September - 1936 June (Volume 29)
  - 1936 September - 1937 June (Volume 30)
  - 1937 September - 1938 June (Volume 31)
  - 1938 July - 1939 June (Volume 32)
  - 1939 September - 1940 June (Volume 33)
  - 1940 September - 1941 June (Volume 34)
  - 1941 September - 1942 June (Volume 35)
  - 1942 September - 1943 June (Volume 36)
  - 1943 July - 1944 June (Volume 37)
  - 1944 July - 1945 July (Volume 38)
  - 1945 September - 1946 June (Volume 39)
  - 1946 July - 1947 June (Volume 40)
  - 1947 July - 1948 July (Volume 41)
  - 1948 July - 1949 June (Volume 42)
  - 1949 July - 1950 June (Volume 43)
  - 1950 July - 1951 June (Volume 44)
  - 1951 July - 1952 June (Volume 45)
  - 1952 July - 1953 June (Volume 46)
  - 1953 July - 1954 June (Volume 47)
  - 1954 July - 1955 June (Volume 48)
  - 1955 July - 1956 June (Volume 49)
  - 1956 July - 1957 June (Volume 50)
  - 1957 July - 1958 June (Volume 51)
  - 1958 July - 1959 June (Volume 52)
  - 1959 September - 1960 June (Volume 53)
  - 1960 August - 1961 August (Volume 54)
  - 1961 August - 1962 June (Volume 55)
  - 1962 September - 1963 June (Volume 56)
  - 1963 August - 1964 June (Volume 57)
  - 1964 July - 1965 June (Volume 58)
  - 1965 September - 1966 June (Volume 59)
  - 1966 September - 1967 June (Volume 60)
  - 1967 September - 1968 June (Volume 61)
  - 1968 September - 1969 June (Volume 62)
  - 1969 September - 1971 April (Volume 63)
  - 1971 April - 1972 June (Volume 64)
  - 1972 September - 1974 June (Volume 65)
  - 1974 September - 1976 May (Volume 66)
  - 1976 August - 1978 June (Volume 67)
  - 1978 September - 1980 June (Volume 68)
  - 1980 August - 1981 May (Volume 69)
  - 1981 September - 1982 June (Volume 70)